<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="levelone">Choose a higher number. \nQuestions can be repeated until you reach 20 points.</string>
    <string name="leveloneEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
        Did you know that the number 7 is considered the luckiest number. There are 7 days a week, 7 continents, 7 colors of the rainbow, 7 musical notes, 7 days of Creation and much more.
        Also, the number 7 is most often the favorite chill of people all over the world.</string>
    <string name="leveltwo">Choose a Roman numeral that is larger. \nThe questions may be repeated until you reach 20 points.</string>
    <string name="leveltwoEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
        Did you know that there is no zero in Roman numerals</string>
    <string name="levelthree">Which animal shows its tongue more? \nThe questions may be repeated until you get 20 points.</string>
    <string name="levelthreeEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
         Did you know that when a woodpecker strikes a tree with its beak, it draws in its tongue and wraps it around its brain to protect it.</string>
    <string name="levelfour">Choose something edible. \n
        The questions can be repeated until you reach 20 points.</string>
    <string name="levelfourEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that the most popular fruit in the world is the tomato! For those who are not in the know - tomatoes are classified as fruits, and they consist of 94.5 percent water.</string>
    <string name="levelfive">Choose something alive. \nQuestions can be repeated until you get 20 points.</string>
    <string name="levelfiveEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that a tooth is the only part of the human body that is not capable of self-healing?</string>
    <string name="levelsix">Choose a higher number. \nQuestions can be repeated until you reach 20 points.</string>
    <string name="levelsixEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that different peoples have different attitudes towards even and odd numbers. For example, we have to give a girl a bouquet with an even number of flowers - either a terrible tactlessness, or a frank death wish. And Europeans and Americans believe that the "even" bouquet brings happiness.</string>
    <string name="levelseven">Choose a fruit. \n Questions may be repeated until you reach 20 points.</string>
    <string name="levelsevenEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that coconut is actually not a nut, as is commonly thought, but a stone fruit. Its closest relatives are plum, apricot and peach.</string>
    <string name="leveleight">Pick a truck. \nQuestions can be repeated until you reach 20 points</string>
    <string name="leveleightEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that gasoline-powered cars were invented later than electric vehicles!</string>
    <string name="levelnine">Choose a city. \nQuestions can be repeated until you get 20 points.</string>
    <string name="levelnineEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that in Reykjavik they make heated sidewalks to turn rain and snow into ice in winter!</string>
    <string name="levelten">Choose useful. \nQuestions can be repeated until you reach 20 points.</string>
    <string name="leveltenEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that lemons have more sugar than strawberries. Lemon contains 70%, and strawberries only 40%.</string>
    <string name="leveleleven">Choose a planet. \nQuestions can be repeated until you get 20 points.</string>
    <string name="levelelevenEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that a day on Mars lasts almost the same as on Earth - only 37 minutes longer.</string>
    <string name="leveltwelve">Choose air transport. \nQuestions may be repeated until you reach 20 points.</string>
    <string name="leveltwelveEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that air transport is the safest form of transport in the world!</string>
    <string name="levelthirteen">Choose a boat. \nQuestions can be repeated until you get 20 points.</string>
    <string name="levelthirteenEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that the average annual salary for a marine transport worker ranges from $ 45,000 to $ 65,000!</string>
    <string name="levelfourteen">Choose a car part. \nQuestions can be repeated until you get 20 points.</string>
    <string name="levelfourteenEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that the worlds first speeding offender was fined 13 km/h!</string>
    <string name="levelfifteen">Choose the first letter of the alphabet. \nThe questions can be repeated until you get 20 points.</string>
    <string name="levelfifteenEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that the letter "o" is 2,000 years older than the entire alphabet!</string>
    <string name="levelsixteen">Choose a word with more letters. \nThe questions can be repeated until you get 20 points.</string>
    <string name="levelsixteenEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that in Russian there are words with three "E" in a row. There are only two of them - exotic "Snake Eater" and "LONG-NECKED".</string>
    <string name="levelseventeen">Choose a female name. \nThe questions may be repeated until you get 20 points.</string>
    <string name="levelseventeenEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that the sound of a name affects character and psyche.
    Modern scientific specialists have come to the conclusion that human names, or rather their sound, have a direct impact on the essence and psyche.
        This interesting fact about names has been repeatedly confirmed. The less frequent and unusual the name itself, the more attention it draws to a person, and the more destructive effect it has in terms of influence
        on the psychological factor of the carrier.</string>
    <string name="leveleighteen">Choose the correct spelling. \nQuestions can be repeated until you get 20 points.</string>
    <string name="leveleighteenEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that there are more feminine nouns in Russian than masculine words? Linguists have calculated that only about 40.5% of nouns are masculine, 43% are feminine, and about 16.5% are neuter.</string>
    <string name="levelnineteen">Choose a superhero. \nQuestions can be repeated until you reach 20 points.</string>
    <string name="levelnineteenEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know comics are useful! \n
        Many parents find comics to be very harmful to the development of their children.
        But British American scientists have proved the opposite. They believe that by reading a magazine and looking at pictures of superheroes, children develop reading skills and memory faster.</string>
    <string name="leveltwenty">Choose outerwear. \nQuestions may be repeated until you reach 20 points.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentyEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that the poncho was used in the army?! /n
        Multifunctionality was what attracted American Civil War soldiers to the poncho. With Velcro, they sealed the head hole so that
        to transform this outer garment into a sleeping bag, with certain skills they could also transform a poncho into a tent.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentyone">Choose a cartoon. \nQuestions can be repeated until you get 20 points.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentyoneEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that the cartoon "The Little Mermaid", which was drawn by hand, has more than 1 million drawings, 1000 different colors and 1100 backgrounds. And all this without the help of a computer!</string>
    <string name="leveltwentytwo">Choose your school affiliation. \nQuestions may be repeated until you reach 20 points.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentytwoEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that the longest lesson lasted 54 hours. This is the professor of biology giving his lecture. It happened in Australia in 2003.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentythree">Choose an ingredient for the cake. \nQuestions may be repeated until you reach 20 points.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentythreeEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that the longest cake was made in Peru. 300 pastry chefs worked on its creation, and for a delicious delicacy, in the end, it took 500 kg of sugar and the same amount of eggs!
        The length of the cake was 246 meters. Then it was cut into 15,000 pieces, which the little June birthday people managed to eat.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentyfour">Choose a part of a person. \nQuestions can be repeated until you get 20 points.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentyfourEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that the skin is the largest human organ!</string>
    <string name="leveltwentyfive">Choose the correct name for the geometric shape. \nThe questions may be repeated until you get 20 points.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentyfiveEnd">\Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that Euclid himself proved 465 geometric theorems?</string>
    <string name="leveltwentysix">Choose the highest amount of digits. \nThe questions can be repeated until you get 20 points.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentysixEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that 666 is considered the number of the demon.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentyseven">Choose a famous soccer player. \nQuestions may be repeated until you reach 20 points.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentysevenEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that the holders of the golden ball in the entire history of football are often players of the attacking line, occasionally - defenders, but the only goalkeeper who received this award is Lev Yashin in 1963.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentyeight">Choose something you can not touch! \nThe questions may be repeated until you reach 20 points.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentyeightEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that mosquitoes are the ones that cause the most deaths.
        On the conscience of annoying and annoying insects that drink our blood and thereby transmit
        viruses from person to person, the largest number of deaths associated with animals.
        Malaria alone kills 350,000 people, mostly in sub-Saharan Africa.
        although this disease is declining. Dengue fever, another mosquito-borne disease
        became the leading cause of hospitalization and death of many children in some countries in Asia and Latin America.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentynine">Choose things that perform 2 or more functions. \nQuestions can be repeated until you get 20 points.</string>
    <string name="leveltwentynineEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that you have to go through the last level? You will have to remember a lot and work hard to pass it :)</string>
    <string name="levelthirty">Choose a famous soccer player. \nQuestions may be repeated until you reach 20 points.</string>
    <string name="levelthirtyEnd">Congratulations, level passed! \n
    Did you know that the holders of the golden ball in the entire history of football are often players of the attacking line, occasionally - defenders, but the only goalkeeper who received this award is Lev Yashin in 1963.</string>
</resources>